In today's video, I'm going to try and
turn one Salana into $1,000 trading meme
coins in 24 hours. Now, you guys may
have seen a couple of my videos where I
start from one Salana or I start from
$100 or even $10. But today's video is
going to be a lot different because we
are currently in a bare market of crypto
and Salana is sitting at $70. So, to
start trading with one soul and turn it
into $1,000 in this market is a lot more
difficult than it used to be, but I'm
still going to try and make it happen
for you boys.
>> Gatorade.
>> Now, the way I'm going to structure this
video in order to turn one Salana into
$1,000 and show you guys that this [__]
is still possible. it is still easy and
anybody can do it is I'm going to be
starting with new pairs and I'm going to
try and build it up to around two or
three Salana in new pairs and then I'm
going to be able to move over to finer
stretch and then graduated pairs. And
the reason I'm starting with new pairs
is because it's a lot easier to actually
build up a very small port because the
market cap is a lot lower and the
risk-to-reward is a lot higher. So that
is pretty much why. And if you guys see
me trading new pairs and you want to
learn how to trade new pairs, then I
have a lot of videos on my YouTube
channel just for new pairs and final
stretch. You can go and watch my entire
memecoin blueprint that will teach you
everything you need to know about
trading meme coins. And I just wanted to
say thank you so much to all the people
that showed support on the blueprint.
Those were very long and hard videos for
me to make. And I pretty much made all
those videos for zero benefit. I'm not
selling anybody anything. I'm just doing
it for the love of the game. and I want
to see all of my boys get [__] rich
>> here in my garage. Just bought this uh
new Lamborghini here. It's fun to drive
up here in the Hollywood Hills.
>> So, without any more yapping, we can get
into today's video. We are going to be
starting with one Salana. I will keep a
P&L tracker throughout the entire video
so you guys can see how much money I
have the entire video. I'm also going to
show you boys every single time I take a
loss, every single time I take a win,
and every time I break even, I'm going
to keep it 100% transparent. My entire
goal with this channel is to keep it
100% real. I'm not trying to sell
anybody a [__] dream. I'm trying to
show you where the manion at so you can
go and get it. But with all of that out
of the way, we are starting with one
Salana trying to turn it into $1,000.
And let's get right into our first trade
and see if we can flip this one Salana
into some actual mona. All right, boys.
So, we just hopped into our first trade.
I did a.5 soul buy on this Jameson coin.
And basically, somebody just made a coin
on bags generating all the fees and
sending it to the family. And I think
this can run. I'm already up a 2x on
this, but I think it can go higher. So,
I'm going to try and hold it out and see
if we can make a salana on this.
All right, boys. So, I've just
completely sold out of my entire
position on this coin. We made 1.1
Salana, bringing our total balance up
already on our first trade to 2.07
Salana. All around, not a bad trade at
all. I kind of top blasted at around 8K
market cap, but I still held to around
30k. I think this can go much higher.
This can probably go to 100K, so I'm
probably going to be kicking myself for
it. But also, when I'm just starting out
with one Salana, I don't want to be
buying stuff and holding them to the
absolute moon and having all of this
optimism because that can come and bite
me real [__] quick. So right now I'm
just going to try and stack up a couple
of wins so we can actually build up this
port so I can start aping in a little
bit more than half a salana. But now we
can go and try and find our next cook
and hopefully we can get up to around
three or four Salana in the next couple
of trades and don't take too many losses
and let's just see how it goes.
Hopefully I find a few cooks. Let's just
lock in boys. All right fellas. So I
just blasted one Salana into this coin
called Mini Me the squirrel. And
basically the narrative is the squirrel
is going super viral on Twitter and
Instagram. A lot of people are posting
about it. And Salana has a long history
of sending squirrels pretty high. So,
I'm pretty confident in bidding this at
30K. So, I'm just going to see what
happens and let it play out. Hopefully,
we can print on this. And let's just see
what [__] happens, boys.
All right. So, unfortunately, we got
stopped out. A bunch of Kos just started
selling it and sending this [__] to
zero. I was up around like8 Salana, but
I didn't sell anything, so I pretty much
roundt tripped it all. But it's actually
okay because with all these K's out now
and a bunch of these heavy wallets
getting out of the coin, I'm probably
just going to rebid it here and
hopefully try and break even or try and
make some more money on top of it. So,
I'm not too upset about taking the L.
I'm just going to rebid it here and pray
to God that it goes back up. Otherwise,
we take a even bigger loss.
All right, boys. So, I've completely
closed out of my position on the mini me
coin. Somehow we actually took a win on
this after getting completely nuked on
by all the Koss. We ended up making.7
Salana, which isn't bad at all. It's
much better than taking a loss. But as
you can see, the coin did just get sent
all the way back to my average. And I
can't really be bothered holding this
coin anymore. I feel like I've been
holding it for almost an hour. So, I'm
just going to take this 7 soul and try
and find another cook and try and build
up this port to around four or five
salana so we can actually start moving
and making some real progress in this
port. All right, boys. So, I just
bought.5 Salana of this tool coin. It's
currently sitting at 13K and I feel like
this is a pretty free bid, especially
for who deved it. So, basically the
narrative is this guy just made a bunch
of tools for this semi-popular AI game
and he made a coin and posted the CA for
it on his Twitter. And he's also bonded
a lot of coins in the past. He has a lot
of coins that have went to 100k. So, I
definitely think this can do at least
something. Otherwise, we just get
completely nuked on by this guy. But
hopefully today isn't the day for Diddy
to come to me and we can cook on this or
at least sneak into something. I feel
like this is a pretty free bid, but
let's just see what happens, boys.
All right, so I've closed out on my
position on tool. That was honestly much
faster than I thought. I've only been
holding this for like 2 to 3 minutes
maybe max. And as you can see, we made.7
salana, bringing the pore up to 3.4,
almost 3.5 salano, which is not bad
progress at all. But all around, this
was a pretty good trade. This coin
literally went only [__] up and I
kind of just sold on that big peak
candle cuz I feel like that's where a
lot of other people are going to be
selling. But let's keep scanning, boys
and try to build this port up from one
soul all the way up to $1,000. Okay, so
I just bought.5 Salana into this GTA 6
coin. Basically, Rockstar just posted a
tweet releasing the GTA 6 cover for the
actual game. I'm pretty much already up
a 2x. I don't think I'm going to hold
this one until once all P&L. It's pretty
fast and I feel like this [__] can just
nuke at [__] any second, especially
with some of the wallets in here. So,
I'm probably just going to start selling
a little bit here.
All right, so we're just sold out of GTA
6 coin. This [__] was really fast. I was
in and out. We only ended up making 6
Salana, bringing our port up to four
Salana. ball around. Not a bad trade and
let's keep scanning trying to build up
the sport to five salana, boys. All
right, boys. So, I probably just bought
the weirdest coin of the day. I just
bought a coin called Mayhem Cat. And
this isn't actually on pump. This is on
Mayhem mode. And the only reason I
bought it is cuz I saw a [__] ton of
volume. And I don't really see a lot of
Mayhem coins going. And this one, for
some reason, is at 100K. So, I thought,
[__] it. Why not? I might as well just
try and bid one soul into this at 100K.
And also, mayhem volume works a lot
differently. So like a one sold buy
actually creates a pretty big green
candle on the chart. So it's not hard
for these coins to actually fluctuate in
price. So I'm probably just going to try
and hold this and hopefully we can get
like a 2x on this. That'll be pretty
chill. This needs to go to like 300k for
me to get a [__] 2x. But I'm just
going to try and hold it and see what
happens. There's like a 100 people
staring at this coin right now. So there
is a possibility that we do get a 2x on
this.
All right, boys. So, I just completely
sold out of my position on Mayhem Cat.
We made 1.078
Salana on that trade. So, pretty much
I've been holding this for a really long
time. If you see over here, I was just
going straight sideways on this coin for
a very long time. And I was honestly
getting kind of antsy right here and
wanted to sell a little bit, but I just
held through it. And then we got some
pretty big candles and continued to go
straight sideways. But then we
eventually started to climb back up and
we got the P&L on one soul. So all
around my thesis was correct on the
Mayhem cat. We made one soul, bringing
up our port to 5.15 Salana. We are
getting pretty close and we are
approaching that $1,000 mark starting
from $50. So hopefully we can keep
cooking like this. Hopefully, we can
find some more players to bring this
port up a little bit more and we can
start approaching that one bando. I'm
going to try and find some more cooks
and hopefully we don't start taking any
L's and hopefully we can keep building
up this port, boys. All right, fellas.
So, I just slammed.5 soul into this
crabs coin and basically the reason I
bought it is because it's going super
[__] viral on Twitter right now and
there's a lot of vamps in PvP over this
coin and I kind of know I'm in the right
one. A lot of these other kids are just
spam bidding a lot of random tickers,
but I know this is the right one. It's
going super viral on Twitter right now.
So, that's pretty much the only reason I
bought it this low. I'm probably going
to try and hold it for at least a 2 or
3x because of all the PvP. I don't feel
like it's going to go very high. I feel
like all the PvP is probably going to
send all of them to zero. Let's just see
if we can make a little 2 3x on this or
if we just take a fat L.
All right, guys. So, I just completely
sold out of this crabs coin. We only
ended up making.3 Salana, which is very,
very small. But basically, the reason I
sold it was because it was just getting
no volume. And all the other vamps and
PVP for this coin specifically just died
out. So, there was no volume coming into
this narrative anymore. But, we only
made.3 Salana, bringing our port up to
6.48 Salana, which is not that bad, but
it's not that great. I honestly wanted
to make a soul on this coin at least. I
thought the narrative was good, but
that's just how meme coins be. Sometimes
you think a narrative is really good and
it ends up doing absolutely [__]
nothing. But that's all good. We're just
going to keep scanning throughout the
day trying to find some more plays. This
obviously wasn't the play for today, but
we're going to keep scanning and trying
to find some more cooks. Okay, so I just
bought a soul into this Riona coin, and
I would be complet I would be completely
lying if I told you I knew exactly what
this tech was. Basically, the reason I
bought it is because the dev of the
GitHub that the fees are being sent to
is very very already on boarded to
memecoins and Salana. And basically, I
think the narrative of this coin is this
guy made some sort of agent that can
solve captures online automatically. It
really makes no sense to me at all. I
pretty much have no [__] idea what
I'm even buying right here, but there's
a chance of him claiming. And if he
claims, this is free as [__] So, we're
just going to hold it out and see if we
can cook on this. Hopefully, we can make
a couple of salana or at least a soul.
But, let's just see what happens. I'm
going to hold this for a bit and see how
it plays out.
All right, boys. We've completely sold
out of this coin and we ended up making
1.29 29 Salana, bringing our port all
the way up to 6.7 Salana. Now, the guy
the fees were being sent to did end up
claiming, and it did exactly what I
thought it would do. When he claimed, it
just skyrocketed the coin, sending it
from 20K to 60K, and we ended up making
1.3 Salana from it. And hopefully, we
can find some more cooks like this. The
[__] was literally only up. This was
probably the easiest trade we've took so
far, but I'm going to keep scanning.
Hopefully, we can bring this port all
the way up from 6.7 Salana to 10 soul or
$1,000. All around it's been going
pretty good today. So hopefully we can
hit that 10 soul by the end of the day.
All right, fellas. We just hopped into
another trade. I did a.5 salana buy on
this coin called Jax. The reason I
bought it is because it's just a viral
meme going kind of semiviral on Twitter
right now. It's not a huge meme, but
it's got a couple hundred thousand
likes. But hopefully we can get a little
2, 3x on this. Maybe we can make a
salana. I'm just going to let it ride
out. See if we can make any money on on
this. Let's just see if we can make any
money on on this.
All right, so unfortunately we have
taken another loss. We only lost 0.1
Salana. But I think the biggest loss
here was that 15 minutes I just waited
on this coin that didn't [__] move.
But this does happen with a lot of
coins. Sometimes you will buy a coin,
you will be kind of unsure on the
narrative and sometimes you are correct
and the narrative doesn't really go up
or move anywhere and you sell for a
loss. But it's all good. We only lost.1
Salana, bringing our port back down to
6.5 Salana, which is definitely livable.
I'm just going to keep scanning, keep
trading, try to make that back and plus
even more and try and keep building up
to 10 Salana. But we did take a little
loss here, which is no problem. I'm just
going to keep scanning and make that
monan back. Okay, we've entered another
trade with.5 Salana. We just bought this
okay coin. Basically, the narrative is
it's Father's Day and there's a lot of
Father's Day coins going and okay is one
of the biggest father memes ever. You
know when your dad just sends a thumbs
up or he says okay with a thumbs up.
It's a very very recognizable meme. So
I'm kind of top losing here at 8K with.5
soul. I think this can definitely go
pretty high. We're just going to have to
wait and see. Hopefully it can cook and
we do not take another loss on this.
All right. We have completely closed out
of the position on okay the chart pretty
much has slowed down a lot and we
weren't getting a lot of volume but we
still ended up making 6 Salana bringing
our pull up to 7.1 Salana. Now we are
getting very close to that $1,000 mark.
I do not want to stop right now. We are
actually [__] cooking today and right
now the market is pretty hot. So there's
a lot of coins coming out. So I'm just
going to keep scanning, keep looking for
more coins and hopefully we can build
this port all the way up to 10 soul
today. So, I just bought another 0.5
into another Father's Day coin. And this
is one of the more interesting Father's
Day memes. This is also a very popular
meme for fathers. This is the very
common, widely known father meme,
mother. I think this trade is literally
out of pure boredom. I don't know what
else to bid right now. And this is the
only kind of semifunny thing that I've
seen in the last 20 minutes. I'm also
being very selective with what I buy.
So, I'm not just going around buying
every coin that [__] comes out. I'm
only ever buying [__] that I think is
sort of funny or that I think can run.
So, another Father's Day coin. I feel
like these have been kind of overdone,
but I still feel like this one can run.
This one is pretty funny. So, I bought
another.5 soul here at 7K. We're going
to see if this can ride up or if we just
take a loss on them.
All right, we just completely sold out
of our Father coin for6 Salana, bringing
our port all the way up to 7.7 Salana.
We are approaching that 10 soul pretty
quickly. Now, the reason I sold out of
this and didn't hold it for longer was
because I'm noticing all of the other
father derivatives and all of the main
father coins are kind of slowing down
and nobody's really buying them anymore
because the trend just get over
narratives pretty [__] quickly. But
we did make6 Salana on that. We are
getting very close to 10 Salana. It is
getting a little late for me. So I might
hop off and come back the next morning.
But I'm still going to be doing a couple
more trades today. Hopefully we can
round this up to around eight or nine
soul and then finish it off tomorrow
morning. All right, boys. So I just
slammed one soul into this coin called
Shill Soul. Basically the reason I
bought it is because a derivative of
this coin is currently at like 100K
right now. And it literally makes no
sense because it's a derivative of this
coin and this one is sitting at like 6k
market cap. So this is like pretty free
to me. So I'm just going to hold this
one soul here at the floor. I'm probably
going to try and hold it for at least
like a 3x because I feel like this is
pretty free. Otherwise, I'll just round
trip or sell for a loss if this gets no
motion. But hopefully we can cook on
this man. Let's just see what happens.
All right. So, I just sold my entire
position on Shill Soul. And basically,
the reason I sold it was because the
main reason this was actually getting
any volume was because the derivative
started picking up hella motion and went
to like 100K. But what's kind of
happening now is the derivative that's
giving this coin motion is kind of
slowing down and all of the people in
that derivative is selling off. So,
they're making the people buying this
one sell it as well. So, we did end up
making point4 soul, bringing our pull up
to 8.1 salana, which is very, very nice
indeed. I cannot complain about it at
all. And now we are only two soul away
from 10 salana. So, let's try and keep
it pushing and try and stack up some
more bread. What's that? You want a
completely free community and people to
trade with? Don't worry, I got you.
Before we continue the video, I just
want to give a quick shout out to my
Discord server that I'm in all the time
and a lot of new traders are coming into
every single day. The Discord server is
called PF Trenches and I am in here
every single day and all these new
traders are trying to find people to
trade with and a lot of new people are
looking for advice and this is the
perfect place for you to come. If you
ever want to trade with other people or
if you ever want to learn from better
traders than yourself, then you can come
in here, ask any question you want and
there is a load of free tools that you
can come in here and use. All you need
to do is go to the link in my
description and click on the Discord
link and it will bring you right to the
server. The server is completely free.
You do not need to pay for anything. We
are not selling anything here. We are
literally just offering a free service
for new traders and people that want to
come in here and try and make some new
money on. So, if you want to find some
people just like yourself to trade with,
then come in here. It is completely free
again. So, feel free join the Discord
link in my description. Let's get right
back to the video, boys. All right, we
have just entered into another trade. I
bought one soul of this coin called
Scissors. Basically, this is kind of
just another slop tech token. I really
don't have too many hopes for this, but
I still think it can go pretty high.
Now, my one kind of problem with this
coin is none of the snipers that got in
early have really been selling, which
kind of scares me because they're still
holding a lot. And this is actually
something that I taught in the blueprint
series. Which reminds me, if you haven't
watched the blueprint, go watch it now.
But because none of the early snipers or
bundles have been selling, it does scare
me a little bit, thinking maybe this is
just going to start wicking down to
zero. So, honestly, this is just kind of
a gamble. I top blasted with one Salana
and I'm pretty much just praying this
goes to 100k or we take a fat L. But
we're just going to have to see what
happens, boys.
All right, fellas. I completely sold out
of the scissors coin. And bad news, we
ended up losing.9 Salana. Pretty much
losing one Salana there. I don't even I
don't even know why I waited until it
went to 12k to sell. That was very
silly. But no problem, man. This is all
part of the game. We take wins, we take
L's. This was my fault. I lost.9 soul on
that. Bringing our port back down to 7.2
Salana. We're just going to keep it
moving, keep it pushing, and try and
find some more cooks so we can bring
this port back up to 8 soul and then
round it up to 10 Salana. All right,
boys. So, I just put five soul into this
coin called the trader. And basically
the narrative of this coin is this is
just a meme that goes back really really
far in the memecoin trenches and
somebody basically just made a profile
and they're kind of doing like a buy and
burn tech I guess but they made a whole
profile for the meme and they're like
bull posting it on their Twitter. So I'm
pretty confident bidding it here at 9K.
I think this can 2 3x or there's just a
secret bundle in here waiting to diddify
me. But we're just going to wait and
see. Hopefully we can make some bread on
this. Hopefully we can cook up a little
two or 3x boys.
What is this?
>> All right, fellas. We completely sold
out of trader and we ended up making.7
soul, which is not bad at all,
especially on a.5 soul buy. Making 7 is
definitely not bad. I would take that
[__] every single day. And I know I'm
only aping in a small amount, but
something that I noticed is a 0.5 soul
buy actually genuinely works. I feel
like it just works better than aping in
three four soul at the bottom because
I'm the type of trader that would much
rather ape in a small amount and hold
for longer rather than buy the entire
supply and sell instantly. I think that
is super cringe. But regardless, we made
7 soul bringing our port almost back up
to 8 Salana. Let's keep scanning and
trying to find some more plays, boys.
Okay, so we have just entered another
trade. I bought.5 Salana into this coin
called Wendy's dumpster. Pretty much the
narrative is Wendy's is going really
viral on Reddit right now because
they're trying to CTO the actual Wendy's
stock. So, somebody made a meme coin out
of it and it's at like 800K right now.
And Wendy's dumpster is a very very
viral Wendy's meme. But I'm just going
to ride it out and hopefully this can
cook.
Okay, I just completely sold my Wendy's
dumpster for a 2x. We ended up making.5
Salana. I kind of knew this would 2x.
This was kind of free. And this is
pretty much only because the main coin,
Wendy, was just getting so much volume
that this was a pretty free derivative
and a 2x. But also, the reason I didn't
hold this any longer for a three or a 4x
is because it is a derivative. And you
got to remember derivatives are not the
main token. So they are not going to go
as high as the main token and a lot of
the times derivatives don't even bond.
So I'm not even going to risk
roundtpping it. I'd rather just sell for
a free Easy2X, especially on a coin I'm
not super confident in. And that is a
tip and a recommendation for all of you
boys out there. Do not get too bullish
on every coin you are buying. But
overall that is a free trade. We made.5
soul bringing our port back up to 8.4
Salana. We are only 1.6 Salana away from
10 soul. So hopefully we can get that
done in the next couple of trades. and I
don't take any losses on the way. All
right, we are in another trade and this
is just another Wendy's derivative. So
basically there's this guy that posted a
video talking about the Wendy's stock
and he's pretty much just impersonating
Roaring Kitty saying he's the next him
because he's talking about Wendy's the
same way Kitty talked about GME and his
video is picking up a little bit of
traction on YouTube. So maybe this can
do something or people just do not like
this guy and send this to Zero. I really
don't even know on this one. But I'm
just going to have to wait and see and
hopefully this plays out in our favor,
boys.
Okay, I just fully sold this Jackson
coin and we ended up making.7 Salana,
bringing our port up to 9.1 Salana. So,
this means we are only.9 Salana away
from achieving the goal. We are very,
very close and I'm just praying that we
don't take any losses that stagnate our
progress. But it seems the trenches did
pick this coin up eventually. I was
holding it for around like 10 minutes.
But again, we are so close to achieving
our goal of turning $50 into $1,000. We
are only 0.9 Salana away. So hopefully
we can keep this up and don't take any
major losses before we hit that goal.
All right, boys. So I just bought 7
Salana into this clout coin. And
basically the narrative is somebody made
like a community cult with a bunch of
different characters with these clout
glasses on. I think it's pretty good and
it's pretty normie friendly. So, that's
pretty much the reason I bought it. It's
pretty easy to understand. It's an easy
meme to get, but also sometimes buying
on a dip like this at 6K is kind of
dangerous. So, I'm really not too sure
on how this is going to play out. But,
I'm just going to let it ride and
hopefully we can get a 2x or 3x on this.
But my chances are looking a little bit
slim on this token if I say so myself.
All right. So, unfortunately, we have
taken another loss. We ended up losing.3
Salana. This chart was pretty much only
down and they just dumped the entire
bundle on me. It is very unfortunate,
but luckily I have a cool head. I'm not
mad at all. There's not a single angry
bone in my body when I'm trading meme
coins. I'm completely calm. I'm not mad
at all.
But, we did end up bringing our port
back down to 8.7 Salana, which isn't too
bad. It could be much, much worse. But
regardless, I'm just going to try and
move on from this loss and try and find
a quick cook so we can get back up to
that 10 Salana mark. All right, boys. I
just bought.5 Salana into this random
Korean coin. Basically, the narrative is
there's a bunch of edited photos of
really known people and they're just
turning them into Koreans, I guess. I
don't even think this coin is that good.
It just has a lot of engagement on
Twitter. So, I'm just bidding it with
half a soul at the floor. I honestly
don't expect much from this coin. If we
get a 2 or 3x, I'll be very surprised.
But, let's just see what happens, boys.
All right, we have sold out of this
stone coin and we ended up making.7
Salana, bringing our paw up to 9.46
Salana. This means we are only 0.55 away
from 10 Salana. Now, I pretty much had
to sell this because it was just getting
no volume. I kind of expected that this
coin wouldn't really move that much.
It's a very niche meme. And halfway in
holding this, I kind of realized I might
need to blur out the image to the actual
coin. I don't know really what the image
is, but regardless, we made.7 Salana on
that. So, it is looking very nice for me
indeed. I'm going to keep scanning
hopefully. It's getting a little bit
late for me right now, but if I can't
find any more cooks for the night, I'm
probably just going to finish it off
tomorrow. Okay, I know I said it was
getting late for me, but I think we may
have just found a potential last trade.
So, I just bought.5 Salana into this
coin called Meme Street Bets. And
basically, the narrative is it's another
Wendy's derivative, but this time it's
different because the original Wendy's
post that started the entire Wendy meta
got deleted on Reddit. So, this guy made
his own subreddit to promote meme coins.
And I've never really seen it done
before. I think it's pretty good. So,
I'm probably just going to try and hold
it or sell for a loss because it does
look like it has a small little bundle
in there just waiting to diddy me. But,
I think if this guy actually starts
posting on that subreddit and starts
promoting meme coins on it, this can go
pretty high. So, I'm just putting all of
my faith into this dev to not absolutely
diddy the chart. But, let's just see
what happens. I'm actually praying
because we are so close to hitting
tensana and this could be the last
trade.
All right, boys. I've just completely
sold out of this coin and we ended up
making 1.37 Salana on that. And that is
officially bringing our port up to 10.8
Salana. So we have successfully turned
$50 into $1,000 trading meme coins.
>> Budget approved.
>> And gratefully my thesis ended up being
correct. And he actually started
promoting meme coins on Reddit and he's
doing it on a live stream which is even
better. But all around this was a very
good trade. We got in at 11K with.5
Salana and ended up full stacking out at
57K for 1.3 Salana profit. So now we
have officially turned $50 into $1,000.
We have turned one Salana into 10.8
Salana and all around I feel like this
has gone very well and this was a very
good trade for our last trade. So
officially we have turned $50 into
$1,000 trading meme coins. I've done
this over the span of 2 days in a
complete bare market. And I just wanted
to make this video as proof to some of
you guys still trading out there, to
some of you guys still struggling to
become profitable, that it is still
very, very possible. I really want you
guys to be watching these videos and
understand that you can do all of the
things that I'm doing. It is not rocket
science. It is not hard. All of you guys
can do exactly what I'm doing with a
little bit of learning, a little bit of
patience. I promise you, you can make a
couple of bands very, very easily. And
then after you make a couple of bands,
you can turn it into six figures, seven
figures, and go infinitely. It is very,
very possible. It is not out of your
range. And if you guys are still
struggling to trade meme coins and you
want a place to learn, I have a complete
blueprint on my channel. It is
completely free. I'm not selling anybody
anything. And those are my best videos I
have ever made. I put so much work into
them and there is information in there
that you wouldn't get if you went and
paid for a course. And I also just want
to say I'm very sorry for taking a long
break. the market kind of went into a
little bit of a drought and I didn't
really have much motivation to come on
and actually trade. I was actually busy
doing other stuff. But that doesn't
excuse it. We are back now. We are
locked in and we are grinding. And I
just want to say I really appreciate you
fellas that stuck around and watch this
video until the end. You guys really
make these videos worth it to me. And if
you stuck around and watched it to the
end, that just proves that you really do
want this [__] and you want it bad
enough more than everybody else. So, I
do love you fellas. I appreciate
everybody that tuned in to today's
video. But that's going to be it for me.
We have successfully turned $50 into
$1,000. And we'll be back very, very
soon with another video. Peace out,
broies.